<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>education on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in education on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aim High ! Go Low !</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-20-high-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-20-high-low/</guid>
      <description>__  Like I mentioned in yesterday’s blog, I have been doing these weekly R sessions at my workplace and thoroughly enjoying them. And for these session, we decide to do some #TidyTuesday challenges to learn together. Today’s session is about that, my journey to attempt the challenge, attempt a fancy blog around it, and then settling for what you are reading right now. Sorry about that!
So it started with looking at the data, which to be fair is a brilliant one this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</guid>
      <description>__  I you have been reading this blog or know me personally you might know I give a shit (or two) about education, specially the state of education in India. There are a lot of reasons behind it, but it mainly boils down to two big arguments. First, I wholeheartedly believe that quality holistic education, education with the development of the individual at it’s core, is one of, if not the biggest factor to sustainable development in this world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Story Is It Anyway?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</guid>
      <description>__  Collation For a while, I have been working on a project to chronicle the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) movement around the world. and specifically in India. One of the objectives is to understand the major events, stakeholders and how we reached where we did today. The entire process has been an incredible experience with so my many of my assumption broken and my views repeatedly realigned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</guid>
      <description>__  The other elephant While discussing the challenges in the Indian education ecosystem over the past couple of blogs I did not address one key aspect, the pandemic. I don’t know if you have noticed, things are pretty much put on hold right now. The world is waiting for a signal to resume business as usual, and no one is sure when that will happen (if that ever happens).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</guid>
      <description>__  Flashback ! In yesterday’s blog I tried to highlight the fact that the education system in India is a shit show. There is an immediate need for a larger understanding of the ecosystem to bring in any meaningful, sustainable change. With that in mind, today I am discussing one of the ideas currently in the research phase. The issue of child rights and it’s connection to education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Out of syllabus The education system in India has been a tricky space to say the least. The sector as a whole has been historically undeserved and / or has encountered poorly implemented policy decisions over time. This has lead to gaps (read, chasms) in the system which have proven challenging to overcome even after introduction of policies like RTE in 2009 - which you could argue was well-intentioned in principle, but lead to further the clusterfuck and complicate the landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>