<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>me on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>https://thedataareclean.com/categories/me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in me on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thedataareclean.com/categories/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Balancing Act</title>
      <link>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA: I am too late to the writing party tonight. It’s 2136 HRS at the time of me starting and I am fairly tired, might be pretty much garbage. Feel free to skip this one, but I shall persevere!
Learn I can’t sit still, I am always doing something or going to do something. I am a restless being and mostly just stop when I go to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Emo</title>
      <link>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</guid>
      <description>__  Family matters Often while talking to my friends about their childhood, the conversation steers into stories around family vacations, or family history. I am always left wondering why don’t I have any such stories to tell. Did I not have lot of fun as a child in my family? Did I not enquire enough about my family history? Do I even feel connected with my family? If this went dark very quickly, apologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedataareclean.com/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>__  Hello not-so-gentle people of the interwebs, welcome to my blog.
Who am I? I am cube, yes cube, I am a fairly private person and incredibly awkward at times so let’s just go with that. It’s not like you won’t find my name on the internet if you look around, but why offer it myself?
 What is this blog about? Who the fuck even knows? There are a lot of things that excite me; open education, data privacy, cycling, books !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>