<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>me on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in me on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Death</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</guid>
      <description>__  I want to talk about a topic that has fascinated me for as long as I can remember. I don’t remember how young was I when I first understood it’s meaning, but I remember thinking: “Sure, this makes sense.”. And something else that fascinated me was how much everyone hypes it up. I am talking about death. Yep, today I will be discussing the D word and related things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlearn</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</guid>
      <description>__  Rant I have realised that I am getting old now. I am a very morning person who gets up at 6 and sleeps latest by 10 every night, haven’t stuck to it since the writing journey began, but I still make sure I don’t stretch it. Yesterday I worked late into the the night for the first time in years and didn’t get enough sleep. The entire day today I was exhausted out of my mind, to the point I had to take a nap in the middle of the day to feel better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiración</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</guid>
      <description>__  Not a Ted Talk I am going to start today’s blog with a random question. What inspires someone? Don’t worry, this is not one of those self help blogs, I am just curious. Also I was struggling with topics to write about, happens when you are doing it for 18th day in a row
But getting back to the point, what keeps you ticking? Is it support of friends and family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneak Peak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</guid>
      <description>__  I had a fairly fruitful weekend this time around. Went on a couple of great walks, got enough time to relax, wrote a series of blogs on a topic I deeply care about. And I am fairly proud of what I wrote. If you’d have asked me earlier will I ever write anything like this, specially during a pandemic, I would’ve laughed at you. And then I would’ve laughed at myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Basis</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</guid>
      <description>__  It was one of those days today. I woke up late in the morning, didn’t have my coffee, didn’t read my newsletters, just sat down to work as my first piece of action. I love absolutely love my work, but I never want to start my day there. I want to come to it all fresh and breezy, bringing every bit of excitement to start doing my thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Balancing Act</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA: I am too late to the writing party tonight. It’s 2136 HRS at the time of me starting and I am fairly tired, might be pretty much garbage. Feel free to skip this one, but I shall persevere!
Learn I can’t sit still, I am always doing something or going to do something. I am a restless being and mostly just stop when I go to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Emo</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</guid>
      <description>__  Family matters Often while talking to my friends about their childhood, the conversation steers into stories around family vacations, or family history. I am always left wondering why don’t I have any such stories to tell. Did I not have lot of fun as a child in my family? Did I not enquire enough about my family history? Do I even feel connected with my family? If this went dark very quickly, apologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>__  Hello not-so-gentle people of the interwebs, welcome to my blog.
Who am I? I am cube, yes cube, I am a fairly private person and incredibly awkward at times so let’s just go with that. It’s not like you won’t find my name on the internet if you look around, but why offer it myself?
 What is this blog about? Who the fuck even knows? There are a lot of things that excite me; open education, data privacy, cycling, books !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>