<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writing on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writing on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pause and Play</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-10-01-pause-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-10-01-pause-play/</guid>
      <description>__  TL,DR ; I am pulling the plug on writing for 100 days straight to focus on learning new things again.
If you have been reading this blog for the last few days, you might have noticed the quality has really plummeted. I have put across some absolute garbage that I wouldn’t ever want to look at again. But more importantly, I realise the decision to stop is not the quality (which frankly was never that high to begin with) but the will to continue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Crossroads</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-04-crossroads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-04-crossroads/</guid>
      <description>__  I had been sitting for over 30 minutes, pondering what do I write about today. I had a fairly exhausting day and am travelling this weekend, both keeping my mind fairly occupied. I am also sitting with this feeling of being annoyed and thinking, I still have to finish writing bedfore I end my day. Noticing my annoyance I wonder, was committing to 100 days of writing a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Rush</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-31-august-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-31-august-rush/</guid>
      <description>__  Milestone Today marks one month of me writing and publishing a new blog every day. It’s been an insane experience and something I would’ve never imagined myself doing. As I am almost a third of the way into my journey of writing for 100 days. I thought I will do one of those reflection blogs. Share my experience of setting up and writing this blog with everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note to Self</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>__  If you have come here for the first time, welcome! It’s mostly me talking about my feelings and other shit. And if you have been here before, you know the drill. Nothing beyond this statement is going to make any sense.
So if you have been here before you might also know that last week I made a commitment to write for 100 days straight to get over my fear of writing and improve my skills along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</guid>
      <description>__  Yesterday, I took the “brave” step of publishing my first ever blog. It was mostly an announcement about of this journey I have embarked on. Somewhere in the mix was also this GRAND declaration of writing everyday for 100 days. 100 days of stuff which I feel is worth talking about. That’s a lot of stuff, especially when I live alone, talk to just 3 people and have no clue how popular culture works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>