<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>foss on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/foss/</link>
    <description>Recent content in foss on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/foss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Step Zero</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I have had an extremely long week and am exhausted as fuck. Probably just going to steal some ideas from my research and spew some garbage. Let me know if it’s too bad. Or just skip it, I don’t want you to suffer through this.
As mentioned in one of my earlier blogs, I have been working on a report to better understand the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) ecosystem in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</guid>
      <description>__  The other elephant While discussing the challenges in the Indian education ecosystem over the past couple of blogs I did not address one key aspect, the pandemic. I don’t know if you have noticed, things are pretty much put on hold right now. The world is waiting for a signal to resume business as usual, and no one is sure when that will happen (if that ever happens).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Out of syllabus The education system in India has been a tricky space to say the least. The sector as a whole has been historically undeserved and / or has encountered poorly implemented policy decisions over time. This has lead to gaps (read, chasms) in the system which have proven challenging to overcome even after introduction of policies like RTE in 2009 - which you could argue was well-intentioned in principle, but lead to further the clusterfuck and complicate the landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My struggles with FOSS</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</guid>
      <description>__  I love technology I absolutely love it! The joy of possessing a new gadget, trying out a new app, figuring out how pieces of technology operate and customise them exactly to meet my needs. The better something is made, the more there is opportunity to mould it, I am sold! Take my money, please make my life better.
 What is all the FOSS about? On top of all the gifts (and problems) technology has given to this world, probably the absolute best thing in my opinion is the FOSS ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>