<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</guid>
      <description>__  I you have been reading this blog or know me personally you might know I give a shit (or two) about education, specially the state of education in India. There are a lot of reasons behind it, but it mainly boils down to two big arguments. First, I wholeheartedly believe that quality holistic education, education with the development of the individual at it’s core, is one of, if not the biggest factor to sustainable development in this world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</guid>
      <description>__  I want to talk about a topic that has fascinated me for as long as I can remember. I don’t remember how young was I when I first understood it’s meaning, but I remember thinking: “Sure, this makes sense.”. And something else that fascinated me was how much everyone hypes it up. I am talking about death. Yep, today I will be discussing the D word and related things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore Diaries</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</guid>
      <description>__  I moved to Bangalore a couple of years ago and I absolutely love it here. Sure, the traffic is annoying and the cost of living is a little higher than I would prefer, other than that I have very little to complain. One reason is that I moved here from Delhi where I lived for over two decades, and the Delhi I left was nothing like the the one I grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Next?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I don’t remember if I have written on this topic before. But this is what is present for me right now and I am too lazy to check.
I am restless as fuck, like peak restless. I cannot sit still for one minute. I am either always doing something, on my way to do something or planning what to do next. Ask me at any moment during the entire day what I want to do, I have atleast 2-3 things always on my mind I want to get back to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Story Is It Anyway?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</guid>
      <description>__  Collation For a while, I have been working on a project to chronicle the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) movement around the world. and specifically in India. One of the objectives is to understand the major events, stakeholders and how we reached where we did today. The entire process has been an incredible experience with so my many of my assumption broken and my views repeatedly realigned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlearn</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</guid>
      <description>__  Rant I have realised that I am getting old now. I am a very morning person who gets up at 6 and sleeps latest by 10 every night, haven’t stuck to it since the writing journey began, but I still make sure I don’t stretch it. Yesterday I worked late into the the night for the first time in years and didn’t get enough sleep. The entire day today I was exhausted out of my mind, to the point I had to take a nap in the middle of the day to feel better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Sensation</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</guid>
      <description>__  Mistakes I have a big learning problem, learning from my experiences that is. I have to really go to the extreme and be completely smashed to bits before I understand, that maybe I have made a mistake going down this path. It’s still a maybe. And by the time I realise it, I have already invested so much energy and time into the task it sort of becomes a point of no return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiración</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</guid>
      <description>__  Not a Ted Talk I am going to start today’s blog with a random question. What inspires someone? Don’t worry, this is not one of those self help blogs, I am just curious. Also I was struggling with topics to write about, happens when you are doing it for 18th day in a row
But getting back to the point, what keeps you ticking? Is it support of friends and family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneak Peak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</guid>
      <description>__  I had a fairly fruitful weekend this time around. Went on a couple of great walks, got enough time to relax, wrote a series of blogs on a topic I deeply care about. And I am fairly proud of what I wrote. If you’d have asked me earlier will I ever write anything like this, specially during a pandemic, I would’ve laughed at you. And then I would’ve laughed at myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</guid>
      <description>__  The other elephant While discussing the challenges in the Indian education ecosystem over the past couple of blogs I did not address one key aspect, the pandemic. I don’t know if you have noticed, things are pretty much put on hold right now. The world is waiting for a signal to resume business as usual, and no one is sure when that will happen (if that ever happens).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</guid>
      <description>__  Flashback ! In yesterday’s blog I tried to highlight the fact that the education system in India is a shit show. There is an immediate need for a larger understanding of the ecosystem to bring in any meaningful, sustainable change. With that in mind, today I am discussing one of the ideas currently in the research phase. The issue of child rights and it’s connection to education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Out of syllabus The education system in India has been a tricky space to say the least. The sector as a whole has been historically undeserved and / or has encountered poorly implemented policy decisions over time. This has lead to gaps (read, chasms) in the system which have proven challenging to overcome even after introduction of policies like RTE in 2009 - which you could argue was well-intentioned in principle, but lead to further the clusterfuck and complicate the landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reader&#39;s Indigestion</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-13-reader-indigestion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-13-reader-indigestion/</guid>
      <description>__  Reading for God’s sake Greetings fellow reader! Yes you, you are a fellow reader! You are reading this, you can’t take it back now! Welcome to the club! We will force you to enjoy it. Also, a small clarification on the section heading, there is no God. Breaking News! Sorry you had to find out like this. Unless you know someone named God. In that case, my God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split it Fairly</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</guid>
      <description>__  Everything I don’t know if you have noticed, the world has been pretty much going down in shits recently. Look anywhere, there is this long drawn process of alienation (through the structures of society) and polarisation (by the power bearers of the same structures), leading to rise in multiple forms of extremism. Hint: Capitalism. I am not a particularly hopeful person when it comes to the human race as a whole, the current scenario doesn’t help the case either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Matters</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</guid>
      <description>__  For a while I have been wondering what constitutes being a leader, how do you differentiate a good one from a bad one, how do you even evaluate their contributions? Do you lead by example or by guidance? If being a leader means giving everyone the space to have a voice, does it also mean checking with everyone if they have something to say? Does any of this even matter if the only thing that anyone looks at is the final output?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Basis</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</guid>
      <description>__  It was one of those days today. I woke up late in the morning, didn’t have my coffee, didn’t read my newsletters, just sat down to work as my first piece of action. I love absolutely love my work, but I never want to start my day there. I want to come to it all fresh and breezy, bringing every bit of excitement to start doing my thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solution</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</guid>
      <description>__  Friday evening all of us at work were doing another video call, but this time it was not work. We were discussing how everything has changed since the pandemic and what do we miss about everyday life. Some background, we are a completely remote organisation without any physical office space, but people used to meet, work together, learn from each other and most importantly about each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note to Self</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>__  If you have come here for the first time, welcome! It’s mostly me talking about my feelings and other shit. And if you have been here before, you know the drill. Nothing beyond this statement is going to make any sense.
So if you have been here before you might also know that last week I made a commitment to write for 100 days straight to get over my fear of writing and improve my skills along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saving Private Data</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-07-saving-private-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-07-saving-private-data/</guid>
      <description>__  The Interwebs So, I have been contemplating this thought for a while and I don’t know where I stand on this. What has been the collective impact of the internet on our world? I know the status is ever changing, we have come through a lot of movements and I am also a fairly pessimistic person. But I still believe the collective good far outweighs the collective harm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Balancing Act</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA: I am too late to the writing party tonight. It’s 2136 HRS at the time of me starting and I am fairly tired, might be pretty much garbage. Feel free to skip this one, but I shall persevere!
Learn I can’t sit still, I am always doing something or going to do something. I am a restless being and mostly just stop when I go to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Suite Life of Data Stories</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</guid>
      <description>__  Landscape The extensive list of challenges the development sector faces are well documented and understood. One aspect that I beleive is still underserved is the data literacy and capacity of the organisation in the space. In today’s world where data has become such a key factor in of the impact conversation, for good or for bad, it requires more attention. Even when substantial data collection efforts are undertaken by any organisation, the data architecture is always an after thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Emo</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</guid>
      <description>__  Family matters Often while talking to my friends about their childhood, the conversation steers into stories around family vacations, or family history. I am always left wondering why don’t I have any such stories to tell. Did I not have lot of fun as a child in my family? Did I not enquire enough about my family history? Do I even feel connected with my family? If this went dark very quickly, apologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My struggles with FOSS</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</guid>
      <description>__  I love technology I absolutely love it! The joy of possessing a new gadget, trying out a new app, figuring out how pieces of technology operate and customise them exactly to meet my needs. The better something is made, the more there is opportunity to mould it, I am sold! Take my money, please make my life better.
 What is all the FOSS about? On top of all the gifts (and problems) technology has given to this world, probably the absolute best thing in my opinion is the FOSS ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</guid>
      <description>__  Yesterday, I took the “brave” step of publishing my first ever blog. It was mostly an announcement about of this journey I have embarked on. Somewhere in the mix was also this GRAND declaration of writing everyday for 100 days. 100 days of stuff which I feel is worth talking about. That’s a lot of stuff, especially when I live alone, talk to just 3 people and have no clue how popular culture works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>__  Hello not-so-gentle people of the interwebs, welcome to my blog.
Who am I? I am cube, yes cube, I am a fairly private person and incredibly awkward at times so let’s just go with that. It’s not like you won’t find my name on the internet if you look around, but why offer it myself?
 What is this blog about? Who the fuck even knows? There are a lot of things that excite me; open education, data privacy, cycling, books !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>__  Work Experience Researcher and Statistician, CivicDataLab
May, &amp;lsquo;20 - Present
 Using public finance data to investigate, advocate and advance child education and well being in rural India.
 Core Team Member, DataKind - Bangalore
Jul, &amp;lsquo;18 - Present
 Pro bono consulting and community collaboration on social innovation data science projects.
 Data Analyst, Pratham Books - Bangalore
Jul, &amp;lsquo;18 - May, &amp;lsquo;20
 Analytics strategy and architecture for the organisation’s open source and open content digital platform, StoryWeaver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>