<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travelogue on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/travelogue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travelogue on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/travelogue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-30-travelogue-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-30-travelogue-three/</guid>
      <description>__  Have you ever been so blank that you thought of writing about an interesting conversation your parents but can’t think of anything to share?
Have you ever been so blank that you that you are exhausted out of you mind but can’t even think about sleeping?
Have you ever been so blank that you are hurt but don’t know how to fix it or if you even want to fix it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-16-looking-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-16-looking-back/</guid>
      <description>__  Dealing with parents tricky. You have different world views, different perspectives, different preferences on almost everything. It becomes difficult to bring those two lifestyles together, something I have been struggling with since I have come home to visit my folks. There are smaller things like my schedule is a little messed up, I am not getting enough sleep but then also the bigger things like how they respond to the world changing around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-12-travelogue-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-12-travelogue-three/</guid>
      <description>__  Today, I officially complete the one week state mandated quarantine after traveling back to Delhi. Tomorrow, I will be a free bird! But before I get too excited about it, I thought it might be useful to look back and see how I feel about the whole thing. Also, feeling lazy and today’s topic just writes itself.
The tricky bit during the entire quarantine from the get go was convincing my parents, especially my mom, that the quarantine is important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-09-travelogue-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-09-travelogue-two/</guid>
      <description>__  One of the biggest grinds I have with living at home is my parents watch a lot of television. Nothing wrong with that, please go ahead watch as much as you like, enjoy the fuck out of it. But at our home, family time is television time. That means you have to sit with them while they also simultaneously entertain themselves with objectionable garbage.
I on the other hand absolutely despise television, specially the ones that are turned on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-05-travelogue-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-05-travelogue-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Today is my first blog from a different location! I am finally in Delhi, away from the comfort of my study table (right now at my sister’s study table). This whole making the decision of coming to Delhi and everything else around it has been some journey, a metaphorical one before the real one today. I have written about it enough times to refer all of them here, but you are always welcome to read the latest update and track back.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>