<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>development on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in development on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</guid>
      <description>__  Flashback ! In yesterday’s blog I tried to highlight the fact that the education system in India is a shit show. There is an immediate need for a larger understanding of the ecosystem to bring in any meaningful, sustainable change. With that in mind, today I am discussing one of the ideas currently in the research phase. The issue of child rights and it’s connection to education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Out of syllabus The education system in India has been a tricky space to say the least. The sector as a whole has been historically undeserved and / or has encountered poorly implemented policy decisions over time. This has lead to gaps (read, chasms) in the system which have proven challenging to overcome even after introduction of policies like RTE in 2009 - which you could argue was well-intentioned in principle, but lead to further the clusterfuck and complicate the landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split it Fairly</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</guid>
      <description>__  Everything I don’t know if you have noticed, the world has been pretty much going down in shits recently. Look anywhere, there is this long drawn process of alienation (through the structures of society) and polarisation (by the power bearers of the same structures), leading to rise in multiple forms of extremism. Hint: Capitalism. I am not a particularly hopeful person when it comes to the human race as a whole, the current scenario doesn’t help the case either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Matters</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</guid>
      <description>__  For a while I have been wondering what constitutes being a leader, how do you differentiate a good one from a bad one, how do you even evaluate their contributions? Do you lead by example or by guidance? If being a leader means giving everyone the space to have a voice, does it also mean checking with everyone if they have something to say? Does any of this even matter if the only thing that anyone looks at is the final output?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Suite Life of Data Stories</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</guid>
      <description>__  Landscape The extensive list of challenges the development sector faces are well documented and understood. One aspect that I beleive is still underserved is the data literacy and capacity of the organisation in the space. In today’s world where data has become such a key factor in of the impact conversation, for good or for bad, it requires more attention. Even when substantial data collection efforts are undertaken by any organisation, the data architecture is always an after thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Draft | Another Brick in The Wall - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</guid>
      <description>  __  Watch This Space TATA!
cube
Part 1 &amp;amp; Part 2 of the series.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>