<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>teach on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/teach/</link>
    <description>Recent content in teach on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/teach/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Data Are Clean</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-28-tdac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-28-tdac/</guid>
      <description>__  Today I want to talk about a topic that is closely intertwined with my identity, specifically my online identity. I am talking about TheDataAreClean, my username literally everyone one the internet. A couple of place I had to use an underscore at the end (mostly due to my mistake), and I am still annoyed about that. The story of why I picked this name is really short, but I have to fill this blog with some content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Teaching</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-27-teaching-teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-27-teaching-teaching/</guid>
      <description>__  One reason amongst many others I care about the education space is my experience with teachers. When I think back to my school or college, I can remember one, maybe two teachers that had any impact on shaping my academic career. All those interactions just toughened me up to not tolerate a lot of bullshit in life.
To be fair, I wasn’t a great kid either. I was a menace, always talking in the classroom, making difficult for any teacher to teach me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching / Learning</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-19-teach-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-19-teach-learn/</guid>
      <description>__  Teaching Recently I have been doing some R session for the folks at my workplace. It’s only been a couple of weeks but it’s made me think about a lot of things. About how so much of teaching involves learning and relearning, about condensing all the information into meaningful sessions, about how teaching is fucking rewarding and why don’t I do it more often? There is a lot to unpack here, let’s tackle all of them one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>