<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Things</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-02-the-good-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-02-the-good-things/</guid>
      <description>__  Incoming I am travelling to Delhi this weekend, and plan to stay there with my family for a bit. And I have a lot of feelings about it. Feelings range on everything from excited to seeing Delhi again since January, to relaxing a little bit at home, to meeting my sister and so much more.
 Sadness But the feeling that is stronger than all the others is probably sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Cube Policy</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</guid>
      <description>__  Struggle As I mentioned few days ago, I am planning to go back to Delhi for a bit. Just see the family, hopefully relax a little and come back fresh. One thing I didn’t mention is how I am mostly doing this against my will. My family had been raising the point of me visiting for a while, and the pandemic was (still is) making it difficult to travel so I just kept pushing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore Diaries</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</guid>
      <description>__  I moved to Bangalore a couple of years ago and I absolutely love it here. Sure, the traffic is annoying and the cost of living is a little higher than I would prefer, other than that I have very little to complain. One reason is that I moved here from Delhi where I lived for over two decades, and the Delhi I left was nothing like the the one I grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>