<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mental health on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mental health on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Cube Policy</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</guid>
      <description>__  Struggle As I mentioned few days ago, I am planning to go back to Delhi for a bit. Just see the family, hopefully relax a little and come back fresh. One thing I didn’t mention is how I am mostly doing this against my will. My family had been raising the point of me visiting for a while, and the pandemic was (still is) making it difficult to travel so I just kept pushing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore Diaries</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</guid>
      <description>__  I moved to Bangalore a couple of years ago and I absolutely love it here. Sure, the traffic is annoying and the cost of living is a little higher than I would prefer, other than that I have very little to complain. One reason is that I moved here from Delhi where I lived for over two decades, and the Delhi I left was nothing like the the one I grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Next?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I don’t remember if I have written on this topic before. But this is what is present for me right now and I am too lazy to check.
I am restless as fuck, like peak restless. I cannot sit still for one minute. I am either always doing something, on my way to do something or planning what to do next. Ask me at any moment during the entire day what I want to do, I have atleast 2-3 things always on my mind I want to get back to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Sensation</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</guid>
      <description>__  Mistakes I have a big learning problem, learning from my experiences that is. I have to really go to the extreme and be completely smashed to bits before I understand, that maybe I have made a mistake going down this path. It’s still a maybe. And by the time I realise it, I have already invested so much energy and time into the task it sort of becomes a point of no return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solution</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</guid>
      <description>__  Friday evening all of us at work were doing another video call, but this time it was not work. We were discussing how everything has changed since the pandemic and what do we miss about everyday life. Some background, we are a completely remote organisation without any physical office space, but people used to meet, work together, learn from each other and most importantly about each other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>