<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Plan</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-14-work-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-14-work-plan/</guid>
      <description>__  I recently noticed a pattern in my daily blogs, specially the ones which are more personal. I start by telling something about myself, my habits, my way of being, or something else. I follow it up by contradicting myself literally in the next fucking statement. I am still not clear how I always end up doing that. Maybe it’s growth in certain aspects of life, maybe I a don’t know anything about myself at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Productivity Tool Trap</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-06-productivity-tool-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-06-productivity-tool-trap/</guid>
      <description>__  I am obsessed with organisation. Day 2 of being back home, I was already cleaning up cupboards and organising my room. I love when everything is stored in a place made exactly for it. In short, I am insufferable. But leaving that part aside, I love doing the same thing for my work. Using productivity tools to meticulously document and arrange every last piece and then bask in the glory of perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Model</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-03-working-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-03-working-model/</guid>
      <description>__  Work I have only had a little over 4 years of professional work experience till now, but it has been a pretty fascinating journey. The amount I have personally evolved, from the people and places I have been involved with, to all the good and bad decisions I have made is really something. I get this sense of becoming a new person everytime I switch jobs, someone with a better understanding of the world around themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split it Fairly</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</guid>
      <description>__  Everything I don’t know if you have noticed, the world has been pretty much going down in shits recently. Look anywhere, there is this long drawn process of alienation (through the structures of society) and polarisation (by the power bearers of the same structures), leading to rise in multiple forms of extremism. Hint: Capitalism. I am not a particularly hopeful person when it comes to the human race as a whole, the current scenario doesn’t help the case either.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>