<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>development on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in development on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Access</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-17-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-17-access/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - Today’s blog is about a space where my knowledge is fairly limited. Please feel free to point out any stupid ideas I have proposed.
I have had the fortune in some extremely rewarding discussion over the last few weeks. All of these discussion centre around some or the challenge that we are trying to approach in the development sector, civic engagement space. While having these discussions I always found myself landing on the same fundamental challenge, no matter what the sector or problem was being discussed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sure, But</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-29-sure-but/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-29-sure-but/</guid>
      <description>__  I have worked in the development sector for a few years now and will probably do so for the rest of my life. This is the only thing I find worth doing. I have worked with with non-profits, CSR teams, volunteer organisations and more. I am pretty thankful I got to do some of that work I did, along the way I got to learn a lot about how the system of working in the sector works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step Zero</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I have had an extremely long week and am exhausted as fuck. Probably just going to steal some ideas from my research and spew some garbage. Let me know if it’s too bad. Or just skip it, I don’t want you to suffer through this.
As mentioned in one of my earlier blogs, I have been working on a report to better understand the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) ecosystem in India.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>