<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>100days on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/100days/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 100days on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/100days/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Disasters</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-25-natural-disasters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-25-natural-disasters/</guid>
      <description>__  Today marks the third day of my complex feelings around work and culture. I feel like I have landed on something here, even if it’s just a bunch of feelings with no end in sight. And like the other two days, today I am attempting to make sense of all my feelings again. Mostly to go to sleep, leaving all the anxiety on this blog.
One thing to know about me is that I am an overenthusiastic cutlet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Organisations</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-24-creating-orgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-24-creating-orgs/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - Today’s blog is a lot of feelings. Apologies if it doesn’t make any sense.
In yesterday’s blog I briefly touched upon the fundamental flaw of any institution in a capitalistic structure. No matter how hard you try to stick to your principles, working in a society that incentivizes constant production over mindful interactions is always a challenge.
What I am not doing today is discussing how to build an organisation without compromising on an individuals or principles, I have absolutely no experience in that area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Boundaries</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-23-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-23-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>__  I have had a funny history with jobs. I always join a place excited about the idea and the promise of the challenge, but soon get disillusioned by the reality of working at any institution. Sooner or later, the sheen wears off and you are left with the reality that you will need to move on to grow. Is the institute at fault? A lot of times, yes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hype Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-22-hype-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-22-hype-ml/</guid>
      <description>__  Do you know about machine learning? Do you know about artificial intelligence? Do you know that it’s the greatest thing that has ever happened in the history of the universe? Do you know data is the new oil? Are you loosing out on the discovery of the century? Do you want to know the secret? Don’t you need to succeed in your business? How can you have a business that thinks rationally and doesn’t fall for this bullshit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That Kind Of Day</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-21-that-kind-of-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-21-that-kind-of-day/</guid>
      <description>__  Day 52.
Today is probably my first unsuccessful attempt at writing a blog. I have been going through a lot of change recently, coming to Delhi, messed up sleep cycle, too much work and I miss my friends way too much. As much as I enjoy writing at the end of the day, the process has been counterproductive during the last few nights, I have produced some A1 quality garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aim High ! Go Low !</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-20-high-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-20-high-low/</guid>
      <description>__  Like I mentioned in yesterday’s blog, I have been doing these weekly R sessions at my workplace and thoroughly enjoying them. And for these session, we decide to do some #TidyTuesday challenges to learn together. Today’s blog is about that, my journey to attempt the challenge, attempt a fancy blog around it, and then settling for what you are reading right now. Sorry about that!
So it started with looking at the data, which to be fair is a brilliant one this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching / Learning</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-19-teach-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-19-teach-learn/</guid>
      <description>__  Teaching Recently I have been doing some R session for the folks at my workplace. It’s only been a couple of weeks but it’s made me think about a lot of things. About how so much of teaching involves learning and relearning, about condensing all the information into meaningful sessions, about how teaching is fucking rewarding and why don’t I do it more often? There is a lot to unpack here, let’s tackle all of them one by one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drag Me Up</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-18-drag-me-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-18-drag-me-up/</guid>
      <description>__  How do you pick yourselves up after a tough week? Do you relax on the weekend? Make yourself a nice meal? Hangout with your loved ones? Actually, let’s take a step back. What ticks you off? What makes you angry and demotivated? What annoys you to the point of inaction?
For me it’s my schedule, or a disruption in my schedule to put it accurately. I am a creature of habit, and engage in the same simple things daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-17-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-17-access/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - Today’s blog is about a space where my knowledge is fairly limited. Please feel free to point out any stupid ideas I have proposed.
I have had the fortune in some extremely rewarding discussion over the last few weeks. All of these discussion centre around some or the challenge that we are trying to approach in the development sector, civic engagement space. While having these discussions I always found myself landing on the same fundamental challenge, no matter what the sector or problem was being discussed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking Back</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-16-looking-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-16-looking-back/</guid>
      <description>__  Dealing with parents tricky. You have different world views, different perspectives, different preferences on almost everything. It becomes difficult to bring those two lifestyles together, something I have been struggling with since I have come home to visit my folks. There are smaller things like my schedule is a little messed up, I am not getting enough sleep but then also the bigger things like how they respond to the world changing around them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boss Kapital</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-15-boss-kapital/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-15-boss-kapital/</guid>
      <description>__  It’s only Tuesday and I have already had a fairly exhausting week. I had a plan to write my blog a little early today and go to bed on time, something I haven’t been able to do for the past week. But then I was reminded, by the beautiful Twitter, that there is an Apple Event today. There went my entire plan, and I am writing this blog at 11:30 in the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work Plan</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-14-work-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-14-work-plan/</guid>
      <description>__  I recently noticed a pattern in my daily blogs, specially the ones which are more personal. I start by telling something about myself, my habits, my way of being, or something else. I follow it up by contradicting myself literally in the next fucking statement. I am still not clear how I always end up doing that. Maybe it’s growth in certain aspects of life, maybe I a don’t know anything about myself at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free and Open Source Advertisement</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-13-free-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-13-free-ads/</guid>
      <description>__  Today my friend shared a tweet with me which caught my my atention. The tweet was by Kareem Carr, who by the way is amazing and you should follow if you work with R or Statistics, bringing everyone’s attention to the tidyquant package. Apparently when you load the package it serves with an “ad”. But before we get into the whole idea of what this means and why does it matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-12-travelogue-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-12-travelogue-three/</guid>
      <description>__  Today, I officially complete the one week state mandated quarantine after traveling back to Delhi. Tomorrow, I will be a free bird! But before I get too excited about it, I thought it might be useful to look back and see how I feel about the whole thing. Also, feeling lazy and today’s topic just writes itself.
The tricky bit during the entire quarantine from the get go was convincing my parents, especially my mom, that the quarantine is important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violent Streak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-11-violent-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-11-violent-streak/</guid>
      <description>__  I am an fairly (extremely) emotional person. A lot of my life till now, most of it, has been driven by strong emotional decisions. All the my successes, even more failures, friendships and more have had a heavy dose of emotion involved. I love it when good music makes me cry, I constant want to hug my friends, I even quit my job once weeks before a promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitive Streak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-10-competitive-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-10-competitive-streak/</guid>
      <description>__  I am an extremely competitive person. I will stress the fuck out when someone is better than me at the thing I care about, constantly wondering what can I do to get better. But I am not competitive in the way that I want to beat you, more like I want to reach where you are so I can have a great conversation with you.
And I will work really hard to reach the point, a lot of times to my own detriment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-09-travelogue-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-09-travelogue-two/</guid>
      <description>__  One of the biggest grinds I have with living at home is my parents watch a lot of television. Nothing wrong with that, please go ahead watch as much as you like, enjoy the fuck out of it. But at our home, family time is television time. That means you have to sit with them while they also simultaneously entertain themselves with objectionable garbage.
I on the other hand absolutely despise television, specially the ones that are turned on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information Obsession</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-08-information-obsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-08-information-obsession/</guid>
      <description>__  I am obsessed with information. I want to know everything about everything all the time. Be it, newsletters, papers, books, podcasts, I am interested. That’s also the reason why I have not been able to leave Twitter, the only one I still have an account on. The ferocious pace at which information flows on that platform is amazing. Frankly it’s very exhausting, but I am addicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribal Tendencies</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-07-tribal-tendencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-07-tribal-tendencies/</guid>
      <description>__  For all its faults, working in the development sector is fairly satisfying. Not always rewarding, but satisfying. In my short-ish experience working the space for the last few years I was always the “Data Guy” in the office, also the default tech support in some cases. That’s says a lot when I truly believe I am not a tech person in the remotest sense of the word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Productivity Tool Trap</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-06-productivity-tool-trap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-06-productivity-tool-trap/</guid>
      <description>__  I am obsessed with organisation. Day 2 of being back home, I was already cleaning up cupboards and organising my room. I love when everything is stored in a place made exactly for it. In short, I am insufferable. But leaving that part aside, I love doing the same thing for my work. Using productivity tools to meticulously document and arrange every last piece and then bask in the glory of perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travelogue - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-05-travelogue-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-05-travelogue-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Today is my first blog from a different location! I am finally in Delhi, away from the comfort of my study table (right now at my sister’s study table). This whole making the decision of coming to Delhi and everything else around it has been some journey, a metaphorical one before the real one today. I have written about it enough times to refer all of them here, but you are always welcome to read the latest update and track back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Crossroads</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-04-crossroads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-04-crossroads/</guid>
      <description>__  I had been sitting for over 30 minutes, pondering what do I write about today. I had a fairly exhausting day and am travelling this weekend, both keeping my mind fairly occupied. I am also sitting with this feeling of being annoyed and thinking, I still have to finish writing bedfore I end my day. Noticing my annoyance I wonder, was committing to 100 days of writing a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Model</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-03-working-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-03-working-model/</guid>
      <description>__  Work I have only had a little over 4 years of professional work experience till now, but it has been a pretty fascinating journey. The amount I have personally evolved, from the people and places I have been involved with, to all the good and bad decisions I have made is really something. I get this sense of becoming a new person everytime I switch jobs, someone with a better understanding of the world around themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Good Things</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-02-the-good-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-02-the-good-things/</guid>
      <description>__  Incoming I am travelling to Delhi this weekend, and plan to stay there with my family for a bit. And I have a lot of feelings about it. Feelings range on everything from excited to seeing Delhi again since January, to relaxing a little bit at home, to meeting my sister and so much more.
 Sadness But the feeling that is stronger than all the others is probably sadness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-09-01-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-09-01-meditation/</guid>
      <description>__  Note - I skipped writing at my regular time today, and am writing this at 0102 HRS on 2nd September. I was extremely tired today (yesterday) and had to take a nap to feel better. Technically I skipped a day even though this blog goes out before next morning. Does this still count? Let me know what you think!
Consistent Today (tonight) I want to talk about something that has been nagging me for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Rush</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-31-august-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-31-august-rush/</guid>
      <description>__  Milestone Today marks one month of me writing and publishing a new blog every day. It’s been an insane experience and something I would’ve never imagined myself doing. As I am almost a third of the way into my journey of writing for 100 days. I thought I will do one of those reflection blogs. Share my experience of setting up and writing this blog with everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pillar No. 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-30-pillar-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-30-pillar-four/</guid>
      <description>__  I have been thinking of quitting Twitter for a while, it’s one of the only remaining social media platforms I am still using. The other is Reddit, that shit is too sacred. But the thought of deleting my Twitter account has crossed my mind a few times, the negativity that platform radiates is at another level. But that is not what today’s post is about. It’s more about information and the role Twitter is playing in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sure, But</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-29-sure-but/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-29-sure-but/</guid>
      <description>__  I have worked in the development sector for a few years now and will probably do so for the rest of my life. This is the only thing I find worth doing. I have worked with with non-profits, CSR teams, volunteer organisations and more. I am pretty thankful I got to do some of that work I did, along the way I got to learn a lot about how the system of working in the sector works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Order, Order</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-28-order-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-28-order-order/</guid>
      <description>__  I have a small confession to make. I absolutely didn’t feel like writing today. I have been working on a report and for the last couple of weeks and writing the first draft and it’s become a bit of an overload. I was struggling nailing down a topic for today and have started writing this at 22:31 HRS, by which time I am usually asleep, and I still don’t have a clear idea on today’s blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step Zero</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-27-step-zero/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I have had an extremely long week and am exhausted as fuck. Probably just going to steal some ideas from my research and spew some garbage. Let me know if it’s too bad. Or just skip it, I don’t want you to suffer through this.
As mentioned in one of my earlier blogs, I have been working on a report to better understand the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) ecosystem in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Cube Policy</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-26-my-policy/</guid>
      <description>__  Struggle As I mentioned few days ago, I am planning to go back to Delhi for a bit. Just see the family, hopefully relax a little and come back fresh. One thing I didn’t mention is how I am mostly doing this against my will. My family had been raising the point of me visiting for a while, and the pandemic was (still is) making it difficult to travel so I just kept pushing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 4</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-25-abitw-four/</guid>
      <description>__  I you have been reading this blog or know me personally you might know I give a shit (or two) about education, specially the state of education in India. There are a lot of reasons behind it, but it mainly boils down to two big arguments. First, I wholeheartedly believe that quality holistic education, education with the development of the individual at it’s core, is one of, if not the biggest factor to sustainable development in this world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-24-death/</guid>
      <description>__  I want to talk about a topic that has fascinated me for as long as I can remember. I don’t remember how young was I when I first understood it’s meaning, but I remember thinking: “Sure, this makes sense.”. And something else that fascinated me was how much everyone hypes it up. I am talking about death. Yep, today I will be discussing the D word and related things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangalore Diaries</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-23-bangalore-diaries/</guid>
      <description>__  I moved to Bangalore a couple of years ago and I absolutely love it here. Sure, the traffic is annoying and the cost of living is a little higher than I would prefer, other than that I have very little to complain. One reason is that I moved here from Delhi where I lived for over two decades, and the Delhi I left was nothing like the the one I grew up in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Next?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-22-what-next/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA - I don’t remember if I have written on this topic before. But this is what is present for me right now and I am too lazy to check.
I am restless as fuck, like peak restless. I cannot sit still for one minute. I am either always doing something, on my way to do something or planning what to do next. Ask me at any moment during the entire day what I want to do, I have atleast 2-3 things always on my mind I want to get back to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s Story Is It Anyway?</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-21-history/</guid>
      <description>__  Collation For a while, I have been working on a project to chronicle the Free and Open Source Software (FOSS) movement around the world. and specifically in India. One of the objectives is to understand the major events, stakeholders and how we reached where we did today. The entire process has been an incredible experience with so my many of my assumption broken and my views repeatedly realigned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlearn</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-20-unlearn/</guid>
      <description>__  Rant I have realised that I am getting old now. I am a very morning person who gets up at 6 and sleeps latest by 10 every night, haven’t stuck to it since the writing journey began, but I still make sure I don’t stretch it. Yesterday I worked late into the the night for the first time in years and didn’t get enough sleep. The entire day today I was exhausted out of my mind, to the point I had to take a nap in the middle of the day to feel better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Sensation</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-19-burning-sensation/</guid>
      <description>__  Mistakes I have a big learning problem, learning from my experiences that is. I have to really go to the extreme and be completely smashed to bits before I understand, that maybe I have made a mistake going down this path. It’s still a maybe. And by the time I realise it, I have already invested so much energy and time into the task it sort of becomes a point of no return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiración</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-18-inspiracion/</guid>
      <description>__  Not a Ted Talk I am going to start today’s blog with a random question. What inspires someone? Don’t worry, this is not one of those self help blogs, I am just curious. Also I was struggling with topics to write about, happens when you are doing it for 18th day in a row
But getting back to the point, what keeps you ticking? Is it support of friends and family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneak Peak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</guid>
      <description>__  I had a fairly fruitful weekend this time around. Went on a couple of great walks, got enough time to relax, wrote a series of blogs on a topic I deeply care about. And I am fairly proud of what I wrote. If you’d have asked me earlier will I ever write anything like this, specially during a pandemic, I would’ve laughed at you. And then I would’ve laughed at myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 3</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-16-abitw-three/</guid>
      <description>__  The other elephant While discussing the challenges in the Indian education ecosystem over the past couple of blogs I did not address one key aspect, the pandemic. I don’t know if you have noticed, things are pretty much put on hold right now. The world is waiting for a signal to resume business as usual, and no one is sure when that will happen (if that ever happens).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</guid>
      <description>__  Flashback ! In yesterday’s blog I tried to highlight the fact that the education system in India is a shit show. There is an immediate need for a larger understanding of the ecosystem to bring in any meaningful, sustainable change. With that in mind, today I am discussing one of the ideas currently in the research phase. The issue of child rights and it’s connection to education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-14-abitw-one/</guid>
      <description>__  Out of syllabus The education system in India has been a tricky space to say the least. The sector as a whole has been historically undeserved and / or has encountered poorly implemented policy decisions over time. This has lead to gaps (read, chasms) in the system which have proven challenging to overcome even after introduction of policies like RTE in 2009 - which you could argue was well-intentioned in principle, but lead to further the clusterfuck and complicate the landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reader&#39;s Indigestion</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-13-reader-indigestion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-13-reader-indigestion/</guid>
      <description>__  Reading for God’s sake Greetings fellow reader! Yes you, you are a fellow reader! You are reading this, you can’t take it back now! Welcome to the club! We will force you to enjoy it. Also, a small clarification on the section heading, there is no God. Breaking News! Sorry you had to find out like this. Unless you know someone named God. In that case, my God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Split it Fairly</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-12-split-it-fairly/</guid>
      <description>__  Everything I don’t know if you have noticed, the world has been pretty much going down in shits recently. Look anywhere, there is this long drawn process of alienation (through the structures of society) and polarisation (by the power bearers of the same structures), leading to rise in multiple forms of extremism. Hint: Capitalism. I am not a particularly hopeful person when it comes to the human race as a whole, the current scenario doesn’t help the case either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Matters</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-11-community-matters/</guid>
      <description>__  For a while I have been wondering what constitutes being a leader, how do you differentiate a good one from a bad one, how do you even evaluate their contributions? Do you lead by example or by guidance? If being a leader means giving everyone the space to have a voice, does it also mean checking with everyone if they have something to say? Does any of this even matter if the only thing that anyone looks at is the final output?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Basis</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-10-daily-basis/</guid>
      <description>__  It was one of those days today. I woke up late in the morning, didn’t have my coffee, didn’t read my newsletters, just sat down to work as my first piece of action. I love absolutely love my work, but I never want to start my day there. I want to come to it all fresh and breezy, bringing every bit of excitement to start doing my thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solution</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</guid>
      <description>__  Friday evening all of us at work were doing another video call, but this time it was not work. We were discussing how everything has changed since the pandemic and what do we miss about everyday life. Some background, we are a completely remote organisation without any physical office space, but people used to meet, work together, learn from each other and most importantly about each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note to Self</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>__  If you have come here for the first time, welcome! It’s mostly me talking about my feelings and other shit. And if you have been here before, you know the drill. Nothing beyond this statement is going to make any sense.
So if you have been here before you might also know that last week I made a commitment to write for 100 days straight to get over my fear of writing and improve my skills along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saving Private Data</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-07-saving-private-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-07-saving-private-data/</guid>
      <description>__  The Interwebs So, I have been contemplating this thought for a while and I don’t know where I stand on this. What has been the collective impact of the internet on our world? I know the status is ever changing, we have come through a lot of movements and I am also a fairly pessimistic person. But I still believe the collective good far outweighs the collective harm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Balancing Act</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-06-the-balancing-act/</guid>
      <description>__  PSA: I am too late to the writing party tonight. It’s 2136 HRS at the time of me starting and I am fairly tired, might be pretty much garbage. Feel free to skip this one, but I shall persevere!
Learn I can’t sit still, I am always doing something or going to do something. I am a restless being and mostly just stop when I go to sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Suite Life of Data Stories</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-05-data-suite/</guid>
      <description>__  Landscape The extensive list of challenges the development sector faces are well documented and understood. One aspect that I beleive is still underserved is the data literacy and capacity of the organisation in the space. In today’s world where data has become such a key factor in of the impact conversation, for good or for bad, it requires more attention. Even when substantial data collection efforts are undertaken by any organisation, the data architecture is always an after thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Emo</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-04-finding-emo/</guid>
      <description>__  Family matters Often while talking to my friends about their childhood, the conversation steers into stories around family vacations, or family history. I am always left wondering why don’t I have any such stories to tell. Did I not have lot of fun as a child in my family? Did I not enquire enough about my family history? Do I even feel connected with my family? If this went dark very quickly, apologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My struggles with FOSS</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-03-foss-struggles/</guid>
      <description>__  I love technology I absolutely love it! The joy of possessing a new gadget, trying out a new app, figuring out how pieces of technology operate and customise them exactly to meet my needs. The better something is made, the more there is opportunity to mould it, I am sold! Take my money, please make my life better.
 What is all the FOSS about? On top of all the gifts (and problems) technology has given to this world, probably the absolute best thing in my opinion is the FOSS ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</guid>
      <description>__  Yesterday, I took the “brave” step of publishing my first ever blog. It was mostly an announcement about of this journey I have embarked on. Somewhere in the mix was also this GRAND declaration of writing everyday for 100 days. 100 days of stuff which I feel is worth talking about. That’s a lot of stuff, especially when I live alone, talk to just 3 people and have no clue how popular culture works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>__  Hello not-so-gentle people of the interwebs, welcome to my blog.
Who am I? I am cube, yes cube, I am a fairly private person and incredibly awkward at times so let’s just go with that. It’s not like you won’t find my name on the internet if you look around, but why offer it myself?
 What is this blog about? Who the fuck even knows? There are a lot of things that excite me; open education, data privacy, cycling, books !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>