<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>musings on TheDataAreClean</title>
    <link>/tags/musings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in musings on TheDataAreClean</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/musings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneak Peak</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-17-sneak-peak/</guid>
      <description>__  I had a fairly fruitful weekend this time around. Went on a couple of great walks, got enough time to relax, wrote a series of blogs on a topic I deeply care about. And I am fairly proud of what I wrote. If you’d have asked me earlier will I ever write anything like this, specially during a pandemic, I would’ve laughed at you. And then I would’ve laughed at myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Brick in The Wall - Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-15-abitw-two/</guid>
      <description>__  Flashback ! In yesterday’s blog I tried to highlight the fact that the education system in India is a shit show. There is an immediate need for a larger understanding of the ecosystem to bring in any meaningful, sustainable change. With that in mind, today I am discussing one of the ideas currently in the research phase. The issue of child rights and it’s connection to education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Solution</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-09-the-solution/</guid>
      <description>__  Friday evening all of us at work were doing another video call, but this time it was not work. We were discussing how everything has changed since the pandemic and what do we miss about everyday life. Some background, we are a completely remote organisation without any physical office space, but people used to meet, work together, learn from each other and most importantly about each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Note to Self</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-08-note-to-self/</guid>
      <description>__  If you have come here for the first time, welcome! It’s mostly me talking about my feelings and other shit. And if you have been here before, you know the drill. Nothing beyond this statement is going to make any sense.
So if you have been here before you might also know that last week I made a commitment to write for 100 days straight to get over my fear of writing and improve my skills along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stress</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-02-the-stress/</guid>
      <description>__  Yesterday, I took the “brave” step of publishing my first ever blog. It was mostly an announcement about of this journey I have embarked on. Somewhere in the mix was also this GRAND declaration of writing everyday for 100 days. 100 days of stuff which I feel is worth talking about. That’s a lot of stuff, especially when I live alone, talk to just 3 people and have no clue how popular culture works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020-08-01-manifesto/</guid>
      <description>__  Hello not-so-gentle people of the interwebs, welcome to my blog.
Who am I? I am cube, yes cube, I am a fairly private person and incredibly awkward at times so let’s just go with that. It’s not like you won’t find my name on the internet if you look around, but why offer it myself?
 What is this blog about? Who the fuck even knows? There are a lot of things that excite me; open education, data privacy, cycling, books !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>